<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Constant of Change</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Constant of Change</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Linear effort is not the way</title><link>/posts/understanding-asymmetry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/understanding-asymmetry/</guid><description>I came across the concept of Positive Asymmetry and it got me thinking about few things.
According to Shane
Linear games are won by working harder than others. And the harder other people work, the higher the bar.
What is happening here is that you are competing with others so that you remain at least up to their level. The alternative would be to remain on a level below them.</description></item><item><title>Bookshelf</title><link>/bookshelf/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/bookshelf/</guid><description>Leave me alone with a book and the concept of time goes into a state of non-existence for me.
I enjoy reading books on anything and everything. Some of my favorite subjects are
Finance and Investments Business History Technology (Mostly computers and programming) Biographies (Technically not a subject) Classics My rating system ★★★★★ Life Changing. Had a profound impact on how I think or do things
★★★★ Excellent. Learned things I can use in my life</description></item><item><title>Wolf of the Plains</title><link>/posts/wolf-of-the-plains/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/wolf-of-the-plains/</guid><description>Title: Wolf of the Plains
Author: Conn Iggulden
My rating: ★★★
I got interested in Mongolian history and Genghis Khan after watching a brilliant series called Marco Polo on Netflix. After watching the series, I wanted to know more about Genghis Khan who was the founder of one of the greatest empires ever. I also wanted to be entertained so I picked up the historical fiction Conqueror series written by Conn Iggulden.</description></item><item><title>Dark Emu</title><link>/posts/dark-emu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/dark-emu/</guid><description>Title: Dark Emu
Author: Bruce Pascoe
My rating: ★★★
Key points Dark Emu by Bruce Pascoe is about natives of Australia also known as Aboriginals. It is a popular belief that Aboriginals were mostly hunter gatherers who lived a nomadic life. They did not have engineering capabilities, never build houses, were not into agriculture and mostly did not do things that a civilized society would. This book challenges such beliefs and presents a different view based on documented observations by early Europeans and recent findings.</description></item><item><title>First Step</title><link>/posts/first-step/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 21:03:44 +1100</pubDate><guid>/posts/first-step/</guid><description>A journey of thousand miles begins with a single step – Chinese proverb This is the first step.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>I try to figure out what many others have mastered.
By following this approach, I am no longer the person I was and I can say with conviction that I won’t be what I am in the future.
I have been working on self improvement for more than twenty years and I&amp;rsquo;m thankful that I started this journey.</description></item><item><title>Sites I like</title><link>/sites-i-like/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/sites-i-like/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/contact/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Offline</title><link>/offline/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/offline/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>